AAFRIN SHAHANAS

WEB DEVELOPER

+91 9597514711 Pangalore, Karnataka, IN afrinshakila@hotmail.com https://github.com/aafrinshahas https://coders-eight.vercel.app/ www.behance.net/aafrinshahanas in www.linkedin.com/in/aafrin-shahanas/

A motivated developer with 2+ years of professional experience in Frontend Development for crafting intuitive, user-friendly websites. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and responsive design principles in front end development. Competent across modern web Technologies and Frameworks. Equipped with Git version control and driven to create visually appealing user experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Greynium Technologies - Bengaluru

🛗 January 2024 - Present

- Designed and implemented user interfaces using HTML and custom CSS to enhance the usability of responsive UI elements and improve overall user experience.
- Enhanced web application performance and interactivity by implementing front-end functionality using JavaScript, leveraging asynchronous programming and ES6.
- Utilized JSON data formats to integrate with rest API for data retrieval and DOM manipulation.
- Utilized the Versioning tool and collaborated with team members using GIT.

HTML Developer

RR Donnelley - Chennai

🛗 January 2022 - November 2023

- Developed responsive web applications using HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript, ensuring cross-browser compatibility and accessibility.
- Implemented front-end functionality using JavaScript including asynchronous programming, ES6 resulting in improved web application performance and interactivity.
- Collaborated with designers and project managers to create user-friendly interfaces and enhance website functionality.

Medical Record Reviewer

Rapid care - Chennai

June 2018 - December 2021

 Conducted detailed medical record reviews for compliance with regulations, coding guidelines, and documentation requirements.

Virtual Scribe

S10 Healthcare - Chennai

August 2017 - February 2018

• Collaborated with healthcare professionals, offering real-time assistance during patient encounters.

SKILLS



EDUCATION

B.Tech in Information Technology

Alpha College of Engineering - Chennai

2013 - 2017

CERTIFICATIONS

MERN FullStack Developer

Error Makes Clever Academy

March 2024 - May 2024

PROJECTS

% https://bookapp-pi.vercel.app/

% https://actodo-chi.vercel.app/

% https://urbanbazzar-dun.vercel.app/

https://weather-pi-two.vercel.app/

% https://nostra-ivory.vercel.app/

LANGUAGE

- English
- Tamil

AWARDS

 Received the Best Performer Award for the Second quarter of this year(Q2 2023).